Today, I sat down with Daniel Lev, the founder of CoinFlow. CoinFlow is a payment service provider
that uses stablecoins to offer faster settlement of both card payments and payouts for businesses.
Daniel's vision for CoinFlow was inspired by his previous work at e-commerce startups.
He had experienced delays and inefficiencies common in payment settlement
and realized that stablecoins could create a better offering.
Without further ado, I hope you enjoy my conversation with Daniel.
Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners at Castle Island Ventures. All of these expressed by them
or the guests on this podcast are solely their opinions and do not reflect the opinions of Castle
Island Ventures. Guests and hosts may maintain positions in the assets discussed in this podcast.
You should not treat any opinion expressed by anyone on this podcast as a specific inducement
to make a particular investment or follow a particular strategy, but only as an expression
of their personal opinion. This podcast is for informational purposes only.
Daniel, thanks for coming on the podcast. Excited to chat today. That's probably overdue at this
point. I'd love for you to start by touching on what was the premise for CoinFlow? Why did you
guys start the business and what have you hoped to build from the day one?
That's a great question. Quick background is I've been building financial products for quite some
time in the quote unquote fintech space and I've been building crypto since I was an engineer in
college and in between I was at a hyper growth fintech. I was doing a big project in there.
We went through hyper growth, got pretty bloated. So I had some time to dabble on side projects
and I'm starting a side project trend company that was a fantasy sports protocol in Solana.
We got a lot of free users and classic like VC back company that goes free,
try freemium and convert. The free users couldn't convert because everything was on
blockchains and smart contracts. So you need stable coins to buy things when people try to
convert. This was four and a half years ago. So people, you know, stable coins really were,
I barely knew what stable coins were and we're trying to use them in our project and no one
who convert. So we started using on ramps. Those had horrible conversion and I was pretty blown away
how like this infrastructure piece of like, hey, someone wants to pay you and you can't get paid,
like doesn't exist for anyone in the crypto community. So it went down like a huge payments
rabbit hole and then realized that this doesn't exist. And what we were solving for is like,
hey, connect a traditional credit card or any form of payment acceptance to a smart contract.
And as soon as that form factor of like credit card is authorized, you can instantly, the merchant
is being you didn't receive those funds. So that didn't exist. But if that existed, that would
actually like create or magnitude improvement in what exists today in hand processing, which is
you swipe a card and takes three or four or five days for the merchant to get the money.
So I was like, okay, someone should build this, we'll build it in house, built it in house. And
then people started asking us like, hey, who's like your infrastructure under the hood? And
immediately we're like, okay, I've seen this writing on the wall, like I see this before,
because the other startup I was at became a unicorn. It started as a NEO bank that created
their own loan iteration software and banks started asking for it. So I was like, okay,
this is great. Like, I see this before people are asking for this product. We don't have it.
Let's totally spin this out. And my background was building this. So yeah, we built a TLGR,
built out of self need. But like going down the rabbit hole like that self need, we understood
the market and like the general gap for it and decided to dive into it. And since then, it's
just like more and more revelations of like how deeply the system is broken and leaving us like
for tons of room of innovation. You touched on this, but what actually happens with a card
payment today? Let's start there. Yeah, I mean, at a super high level, there's like a few different
players. There's a card network. So your Visa, MasterCard, Amex, Discover, et cetera, your merchant.
So the person that, hey, you were consumer buying something from, there is the issuer. So the person
that issues the cards, the consumer that types your card. And then on the other side of that,
for the merchant, there's a payment search provider, someone like point flow, and oftentimes an
acquiring bank. So someone that helps underwrite and communicate to the card networks,
all those parties have to communicate. And what's gotten really good in terms of user experiences,
people swiping the cards, like the consumer has no issues with that, right? You swipe your card,
you see right away that the payments authorized. So the payment search provider helps the merchant
capture that payment. So within seconds, you know, like, hey, why it has or whoever the user is has
money in their accounts, and it's going to be good. And it will eventually get to the merchants
after that step. So like after it says, hey, money's there, you're good to go. That's where the money
starts moving between all those counter parties. And things happen very, very, very slowly. So
that's where really like the core of it is. And a lot of the, I'd say, industry and innovation has
happened on the front end, making sure that it's like super easy for you, the end user to spend
your money. And even post fact of spending your money, like, you're insured, like if something
goes wrong, you can call to the bank and say, hey, like, I was buying an ice cream cone from Dan,
he promised me vanilla, gave me chocolate, like I should get a refund. So that whole process is like
very smooth. And I would say more or less solved. But for the businesses, like when I sold you that
ice cream cone in this hypothetical instance, it took me three days to get my money because
what happens as soon as it's authorized, then the issuer gets pulled their funds,
which is the person in the bank that issued your card, they get their money pulled,
the card that works the middleman, they give it to the acquiring bank. And the acquiring bank
has to send it to the payment search provider, payment service providers will release those funds
to the merchants. And all those are on traditional banking rails. And if you're doing that transaction
globally, then it's like via the Swift network, which adds counterparty banks. And if there's
one bank holiday in one country or one delay somewhere, then like that whole food chain
gets slowed down. So until the arm. Yeah, it's like a system that's been built for comfort for
the end user with a host of structural debt underneath. That's a very good summary. Exactly.
It's been built for the consumer, the ton of structural debt. But it works for them. So like
the average person is not complaining. Right. And it's funny because one of the pushbacks I get on
stablecoins, particularly in the US is people will say, oh, my card network or my card payments
works very well, like, I don't have any issues. And it's this point that it's built to suit that
person, but maybe not the vendor or maybe not someone else who's involved in that chain.
Yeah, totally. Like I use stablecoins in business, obviously, every day. And our companies is at
100,000 times a day transactions. But as an end user, I use my card in order magnitude more. And
I think that's like because of the rewards, everything else we get with it. So I totally
get that. I don't know if stablecoins will fully replace, I don't want to go on this rabbit hole,
but like, as of right now, there's no stablecoin product that means the end user would rather
use in my credit card for like day to day purchases. But if I'm buying something that cards can't
accept. So like a high ticket item, I'm paying my rent, I'm much rather do that via a stablecoin.
I think rent payments are like a mortgage or a car payment. So like that, that's larger that
someone won't accept a credit card for that makes sense with the stablecoins. So
I totally get what your friends are people are coming from. So how does coin flows workflow
compare to the traditional payments networks that you mentioned? Yeah, so in that process,
let's just go back to that ice cream shop example, I own an ice cream shop, I sell you ice from cone.
In that traditional example, I say we're using like a legacy provider, let's call it like Stripe.
As soon as you swipe your card, and it says hey authorized ice cream cone, and I give you the
ice cream cone, then it takes Stripe has to release those funds. Once they get it, let's say they get
it instantly from their bank, which isn't possible, say they do, they still have to release those funds
to me the ice cream owner, and some type of bank payment. Let's call that ACH because that's most
banks, not all banks take real time payments, it's going to be ACH. That takes one to three
business days. It's Tuesday, so a quick guess, I'll get my money on Wednesday evening, but likely
Friday. So that's like, if I'm the ice cream shop owner using Stripe, so I'll get my money
one to three days from when you paid. And coin flow, what we do is as soon as like you swipe
your card, we get that authorization, because we know the money is coming from the card networks,
like we trust Visa will give us the money, they're legally obligated to. So as soon as the card
swipe happens, we instantly settle funds to the ice cream shop's owner in their digital wallet
via stablecoins, it looks like a bank dashboard, where they have money in their wallet, it says
US dollars. And then if they hit withdraw, if they want to move it to their bank account,
we can then instantly pay out to that bank account or do it through that same bank payout
method. So it's just they're instantly can be used, we can attach a credit card and to the spend,
it can be sent cross board, it can be done with whatever they send it to another vendor,
whatever it is. So that's the difference, instead of waiting like one or three business days, they
get their money in five seconds. Are you guys funding that leg off of your balance sheet,
or do you have access to a line of credit, or how do you ensure that you can maintain that
instant settlement when you might have times where there's a lot of flow coming in?
Yeah, a little bit of all the above. Some of it's balance sheet capital, some of it is like
partner capital. And then a lot of it is payouts as well. So we get tons of payouts of people
like, Hey, like, I actually don't need my money for three days. So I'm going to choose a cheaper
payout option. Like I think yesterday we had like a $10 million, I think a state of wire,
and they're like, Yeah, like we need to get the funds on Friday. So that goes into our liquidity
engine. And that ice from shop owner can leverage that that goes into play as well, a little bit
of all above. And then the cool thing is that we are starting to get settlements from our
acquiring banks, not in the US yet, but in Europe via sample coins, five days a week. And visa is
rolling that out seven days a week. So yeah, like, not only is it structurally an issue that
payment service providers can't give their merchants funds 24 times 365, but the card
networks don't actually have ways to access send their payment service providers a coin flow. Like,
let's say this was let's go back to the stripe example. If visa wanted to settle faster, they
actually couldn't like we're aware right now without stable coins. So visa and other card
networks are rolling about pilots. And we're starting to settle get those funds seven days a
week. It's not going to be t plus five seconds like coin flow doesn't but that window on like
fronting it goes down. So there's definitely some man behind the curtain going on that we're solving
for with both like financial products balance sheet, our own liquidity engine. But it's cool to see
that gap diminish. And we have all the infrastructure and technology to manage those different ledgers
because you're managing an instant ledger, which is the blockchain with traditional rails. So you're
connecting those two together, not only moving money between them, but like connecting those two
ledgers and marrying them together, which have all done on house and like battle test out scale.
And maybe sit in the obvious, your guys job would become much easier if
initial payments actually started to become made in stable coins, because then you just become an
orchestrator of stable coins to whoever the end recipient is, or the middle band that you need
to route to, correct? Yeah, that's right. Like we take in the table coin payments today. I don't
know if much easier, it's just a little bit different. Like we orchestrate between a bunch of
different payment methods. And in no world is there going to be like one payment acceptance
winner of some type of method, right? Like today, even for example, we have merchants who 95% of
their volume of credit cards, but they still have like 3% acceptance and bank payments. And then
like 2% acceptance in stable coins, whatever it is. And even though like in my mind, bank payments
is a way should your options pay for like, I don't know, this is a red bull, like to buy a red bull,
right? But if 3% of your users want to do it, you're not going to be like, Oh, no, screw 3%
of my revenue. I'm not going to accept it. So the job of people like coin flow is going to be
accept a larger amount of payment options and continue to drive the speed of the settlement
down to closest instant. So I think that's why like stable coins, I'm so bullish as an infrastructure
play, because it's really the only way to connect all these very disparate systems and get as close
to real time as possible for settlement. I'm a believer that over time, we'll have more rather
than less payment methods too. When a lot of these software companies become fintechs at the same
time, and you have money accounts associated with a lot of them, and you'll probably have a rise of
more digital banks, curious for your perspective, but that's the way I see things going 100%.
There's more and more payment networks. So like, yeah, I guess like that digital bank example
you called out, or apps that become like more fintech that you can pay with those balances.
See, I think there's going to be more and more payment networks, both crypto networks,
traditional fintech networks, et cetera. But there needs to be a way to like interoperate them,
because the goal of if you have money in an account, those people want to monetize in those
balances. And the only way to monetize on them is one, keep them in there, or two, like allow them
to spend those balances. So if they spend those balances, they need a way to transact. And like,
the only way to do that easily globally is either through like issuing a card off the balance,
or through making a stable money transfer. So you touched on payouts, and we've talked about
payments acceptance. Could you highlight CoinFlow's range of offerings? And at the same time,
where you guys have gone based on where you see gaps in offerings from Stripe,
Addian, Shift4, and larger existing payments players?
Yeah, for sure. I would say there's like two main products. One is like allowing
our merchants to accept payments globally, and instantly receive funds instead of waiting
multiple days. So like all those people you said, at least one or two business days to get
your money, we do in five seconds. And then also, none of them help you like,
get rid of fraud, they help you prevent some of the fraud, the difference between CoinFlow is like,
we'll eat all the chargeback risk. So the value prop is like, Hey, get your money instantly, and
don't lose any money to fraud. So that's what the payment step is inside. But once you get your money,
a lot of businesses, marketplaces, remittance companies, gaming companies, crypto exchanges,
anything that has consumers that need to cash out, fintechs, etc. will not only receive money
for end users, but need to pay out to their end users. So there's a payout component,
and that's other product. We have that in like 70 plus countries. I would say the biggest gap
that we've seen in the market is combining those two products together. So when all those types
of companies, like especially marketplaces, where you have, let's say that ice cream shop example,
let's say there is, I don't know, digital marketplace for ice cream shops, and you can buy
these gift cards. Now I'm the marketplace, and I have all these sellers on my site,
you're buying stuff from them. So not only do I have end users consuming and spending,
you also need to go pay out these ice cream shop owners, and they could be globally.
So I think connecting those two products between ledgering, holding funds on platform,
which is very easy to like digital wallets, fraud, etc. That's probably the biggest gap
we've seen in the market. And then there's just a lot of payout gaps. Because of the
how prefunding works. So kind of stable coins to that has been like a huge, huge win. I'll give
you an example. So like say you are a business in the US and you're to pay out suppliers over the
weekend or whatever it may be, you can pay people out through Visa direct, if they're small purchases
up to 50 grand, Visa direct, so you enter your debit card and get paid out, or real-time payment
network. But to get there, you actually pre-fund the main account to be a buyer. So like before
5pm on Friday. So if you don't get your wire in like 2pm on Friday, you actually can't use a real-time
payment network. So it's kind of contradicting. Let's say you don't get your wire in, but you send
stable coins to us. That's still a proof of good funds. We know that money's there. And then we can
burn those funds and then pay off from that balance over the weekend. So this like pre-funding
dilemma has more or less been solved if you can use stable coins or payouts. So that's another big
gap. I think the biggest gap is still that like collecting the pay in and payout piece and making
both instant. People have done a good job of making like the payout piece instant by pre-funding.
But it's not like all that instant if you have to use your own balance sheet or somehow figure
out a way of pre-fund before bank hour close. Yeah, definitely. That example's helpful. Makes a lot
of sense. You touched on the fraud piece. I think that's easy to overlook. How do you guys eat the
risk of fraud that seems very attractive if I were a vendor, for example? Yeah, I know. It definitely
is. So the play really is like it's an AI model and it's a mix between like insurance and a fraud
model. It's going more and more towards like the fraud model and insurance is like making sure that
we can cover it fully. But yeah, the fraud model has like 100,000 variables and it's an AI model.
So it continuously learns as fraud attacks happen. Fraud is like a cat and mouse game where like
you find the problem, you stomp it and then like they come back like whatever in their role,
hopefully in months or years later, but they keep finding new routes. And that's why like the AI is
so helpful because if you have a deterministic model, so for example, like what that means is hey,
why it is a fraudster and he is figuring out that I'm the ice cream shop owner and if I buy a $500
ice cream cone or more, we actually don't do any checks because we think that's like a VIP customer.
They want gold sprinkled in the ice cream cone and that's like super low risk to us. So say you
was why the fraudster figured that out and only buy gold sprinkled ice cream cones now.
Me as an ice cream shop owner in like two, three weeks, I get those chargebacks will figure out like,
oh, hey, like maybe we actually shouldn't allow people to buy $500 ice cream cones or do like really
strong KYC, make why it tell us his kid's first name, do an eyeball scan, which is going to kill
conversion. So that's why these deterministic models don't really work because like sure,
you can stop it, you can find out what's happening, duct tape it, but when you duct tape it, you
actually kill real users. But these AI models will learn really quickly like, okay, like we used to
only sell one gold plated ice cream cone a month, we sold 10 today, like what is going on? And the
model will learn, hey, saying this is suspicious activity, let's stop it. The other beauty is
like the blockchain and what the card networks are starting to embrace and have at least these
put in the rules is something like proof of deliverability. So in the ice cream example,
it doesn't really work well because it's a physical good. Well, let's just say like a digital good,
a Fortnite skin is a good example. If you were dispute right now in Fortnite, like, hey, I didn't
get my skin, there's really no good way for the card network to have insight into if that good
was delivered to you because it's a digital good, how that good is delivered is a switch in
Fortnite's database like saying, hey, why it's a count? Why is it beast? Now it has the dragon
skin. Very, very hard to prove because like Fortnite is not going to be like, hey, here visa,
here's my database keys, go see this, they'll just show like an email receipt. It can be altered,
it's not very good and doesn't win. With blockchain, everyone can see it, including the PSP, that the
item was delivered right away, if it's shown on chain. So you can actually see the transaction
happen like, hey, why it paid with the card, funds were settled to the merchant, and that same
transaction that skin was released. That transaction can be attached to the payment to visa while the
transaction happens. So if a dispute then later happens, we can be like, hey, no, why saying he
never got this? Look, look visa, look bank, that was actually given. So that's still like very
early days. But for a lot of use cases, like the digital goods, it works very well. It even works
better for things like remittance, or when people are popping up into accounts, for example, like
adding money to an exchange, very hard to argue if you have a wallet that has received sample coins,
that you didn't actually get the sample coins. It's very easy to prove in a matter of seconds,
and you can tie it to the exact transaction. So there's a ton of innovation happening there
behind the scenes, which isn't like talked about, because when it's early, and it's not sexy. But
I read something the other day that like $100 billion of losses happened to merchants last year
just by friendly fraud. What that means is like, people know that if they call our bank and complain
that something wasn't right with the thing they bought, the bank will likely start with them,
which is called friendly fraud, even though that, hey, like this Red Bull tasted funny.
The bank will probably honor that. And now the merchant has a charge back. And I as a consumer
just got my like $5 back for this Red Bull. So yeah, there's a lot of like innovation happening
there. And I'm excited to see I think it will like definitely be a sleeper to look for in the next
few years. Yeah, I mean, from my perspective, there are just multiple layers of compensation
and issues happening. Like the banks are willing to eat that because they get to keep essentially
all of the interest or whatever they're making on your deposits and that business is too good.
So it'll pay you back for your Red Bull. But realistically, then in a way, it becomes the
and merchant losing, which is a messed up system. So there's a lot to be fixed. A single ledger
to your point is very attractive. I think when it comes to tracking something like fraud,
have you guys built your fraud engine in-house or what are you using?
Yeah, I'd say our fraud engine is in-house. And then like any other fintech, we bundled like
10 different providers. See, we have a bunch of different providers, whether like we're using
even like some AI models, we have Gemini, we have another platform that has their own
AI model called insure.ai. We use them for part of the insurance. We have our own engine that
plugs into all these things and calculates the risk of fraud. Plus, a lot of it is like data
orchestration to fintech's models. So yeah, I think like most things in fintech are built
as close to the rails as possible and orchestrated together without end users knowing anything's
there and it just works. In the backdrop of some innovation similar to what we've been talking
about where you're having more pay with crypto cards, pay with stocks, pay with treasuries type
payment cards, do you think the fraud tooling and infrastructure or anti-fraud mechanisms
are getting better? Are you seeing interesting innovation on that front, especially when it comes
to more on-chain assets, more assets of different types, et cetera?
I would say they're getting better. Nothing has been like fully cracked yet. And I think it's
because it's so early and only the last year or two have been like a new wave of companies
building and innovating just generally around like the stablecoin space. Like there's market
leaders like Coinbase, Circle, Tether. There's people doing it, but now we have hundreds of companies
and when you're a market leader like Coinbase, Tether, whatever, Circle, you will have your
own fraud teams. Sure, you need this infrastructure group at some point. You're like, this doesn't
exist. We're just going to have our own team building internally. But when there's hundreds of
thousands of companies already in this type of technology, every company can't just have their
own fraud team figure it out. You want to use infrastructure providers or at least supplement
it. So I think that's where the innovation is stemming of like, okay, now there is a bunch of
demand for people to build this type of apps or infrastructure and then there'll be other
infrastructure to support it. So that's what we're seeing here. I think it's still pretty early days,
though. That makes sense. And it seems like over time, regardless, these more complex types of
transactions like global are going to be more advantaged. I was curious to ask you in that vein,
how much of what you guys do is US to non US or non US to US versus domestic?
Yeah, I think we're probably a very unique spot in terms of most stable coin companies,
quote unquote, right? Most of our volumes US probably at least 75% is like both pans and
pads are domestic. And it just shows because like, our banking rails are so archaic and so slow
that yeah, speeding up payments, using a better rail in between is an example. I think like the
best example is our biggest category now is marketplaces. So when there's a merchant is the
marketplace and there's buyers and sellers on both sides. This is for digital goods or rail goods
or could be either? It can be anything. It can be anything. I think the issue with these companies
right now is the money movement's very slow. And you tell any marketplace, like I got my hair cut
this week, and I used a marketplace called Squire. It's a place for barbers. So my barber,
instead of like setting up a strike account, managing taxes, managing like the booking,
Squire does that Squire is a marketplace and all the barbers have to do is go sign in.
He enters the dates and you can pay there. You can do everything there. On Squire, they use
Stripe. My barber gives me a haircut on Friday. I pay via Stripe. He gives us money Tuesday.
I asked that same barber, like, Hey, would you want to get paid today? His answer is going to be
like, Yes, I want to get paid today. My girlfriend and my friends want to go get drinks. I would
love to use the money I made today from your tip to go buy everyone drinks. Can't happen, right?
Coincidentally, Stripe, most of their volume and things sign up for their volume or something,
60 to 75, I don't know exact numbers, majority comes from their marketplace product.
So you can think about this as like everyone who's selling an item through that marketplace
is like, Hey, I want to get my money faster. And they can't. And that's all domestic. Like,
my barber is domestic, et cetera. And that's Stripe's volumes mainly domestic too.
So the long story is most of all in the US, unlike most stablecoin companies,
but there's still huge things that are broken in very large industries like marketplaces
in the US that just having a stablecoin in the back end can make way more efficient.
In that example, do you think the cost of delivering a free payment will come down to zero
or an instant payment, I should say? Or do you think that there will be some kind of a credit
market there where you're paying some rate in order to get instant payments versus whatever
would be a two, three day latency? I don't think it'll go to zero because it doesn't need to go
to zero. Consumers are willing to pay a lot like right now a lot of money for it, right? Like,
I don't know what the average rate to borrow is right now, but it's 8% for a year-ish, right?
Like, even if you're a small business, yeah. It's called like 8 to 10, right? Let's call it 10
high side. Consumers are paying like 200 base points, 2% to get one payment instantly from like
Venmo, Coinbase, Cash App, et cetera. And most people on Venmo are doing the instant payments.
That's in the US. So like every time they receive a payment, that's 2%. So that like one payment
that they just paid for instant payment is 25% of like the cost of capital to take that as a business
for a year. So you can think about how many times they could get recycled and sure it might be cheaper,
but it won't go to zero because people are just willing to pay for it. And if it's like marginally
more expensive, let's call it like instead of 2% of people, majority of people in Venmo are willing
to pay 2%, let's cut it 90% and call it like 20 basis points. I still saw it in margin and on the
credit market, it's still pretty good for one transaction. So I think there's like a lot of
room to play with even if it goes down 90%. Yeah, I completely agree. In the three years you've been
working on in this area essentially, how has the environment around you changed both from a perspective
of companies and regulatory attitudes? Yeah, I mean companies, there wasn't many people building
this. It was all very crypto centric. I would say infrastructure was only being, I mean people
talked about like letting non crypto customers use crypto rails. Since I've been in crypto for
the last like decade, like, oh, you like people are going to use Bitcoin or people are going to use
this and that same thing in stablecoins, like there was some, I think the 2020 bull market saw some
of that people come on chain or businesses come on chain primarily NFTs and I think a lot of them
like PR stunts, even ones that did wall got shut down like DraftKings had an NFC marketplace that
did pretty well and they shut it down or it did really well relative to other NFC marketplace and
they still shut it down. It probably didn't do as well as their actual business that makes money.
So there just wasn't many businesses servicing anything outside of crypto and crypto was just
really down. But I think there was like a cohort of believers of like, hey, like this core infrastructure
does work. And it's just a matter of time. And then between like the 2021-2022 bear market happened
or like bull market ended to a bear market. It was pretty crazy because
most people that were building infrastructure were servicing crypto companies. A number of
crypto companies went down. So like your core ICP shrunk. And then not only that happened,
but regulatory environment got more hostile. So if you're building in something that's like
financial, they were cracking down on banks in the US plus on crypto. So like your ICP is going down
and people are out to get you. So that was a pretty crazy time the last few years. And then
I would say like right around the Trump election, some companies started getting scale using stable
coins as infrastructure. The larger companies weren't slowing down. And more and more
companies like CoinFlow and others started getting traditional web two businesses to
use and adopt these tools. And then I think there's a bunch of catalysts, but probably the Trump
election just sparked a huge insurgence of like businesses wanting to learn more about
stable coins, using stable coins. And then you basically saw like every major fintech.
And even some before the Trump admin like PayPal is one that you can call out because like
they launched PayPal, USB and started talking about stable coins during the Biden administration,
et cetera. But then there's a little, and Vista was doing this, there was only a few you could call
out and I was on banks like, Hey, look, PayPal is doing it. Vista is doing it. Trust me, it's
going to be a thing. And then so people started like looking at it, but they still looked at it
like a little weird or squinted. And then when Trump got elected and acquisitions started happening,
every fintech started now is there is stuff with stable coins came from like sideline to like,
Oh my gosh, everyone has to go and at least do research and development and make a
press release that they're doing research about it. So yeah, huge tailwinds on like fintechs.
And then from merchants or like from businesses that we serve, I would say the biggest change has
been like, they're seeing that news, they're seeing that like, Hey, like this isn't going away.
And consensus is a better tool. I think they were just scared like talking in person about it,
cool, they get all the value process. But then again, the tools are using, they work,
there's a way to optimize it. But the mental model they were looking at was like, Okay,
we can get our money instant. But the thing we're getting the money through stable coins,
even though it's all infrastructure, let's say the biders fishing out elected again,
or whoever got elected, and they were like anti like, they could just make that illegal. Now,
like, sure, we're getting this thing faster, but the company that servicing us came and operating
more. So that's not a huge one. So that risk is out of the picture now for the awesome.
Yeah, it's an important point. It feels like there's a sustainability now.
Dan, in closing, I wanted to ask to that point you just made, if there is a seller of goods,
a vendor out there who is in this paradigm where you take a payment on Friday, you receive funds on
Tuesday, how should they proceed towards trying to iterate towards a next generation, instant
ask payment system internally? Yeah, I mean, they can just talk to us and we can do it all for
them. So yeah, if they want to get in contact with us, we're very reachable, like our website's
coinflow.cash, or you can hit me up on my Twitter, or I'm sure it'll be attached to us. But yeah,
reach out to anyone from the coinflow team, and we're happy to help and map out your flow of funds,
map out your roadmap, etc. But yeah, I think this is where the world's going, because the
value problem is very simple. Like, it's hard to find someone who doesn't want to get paid
for what they're doing as soon as they do it. Yeah, makes sense. Well, Dan, thanks for joining
us and hopefully we can sit down again sometime soon. Yeah, man, thanks for having me. It's been a
pleasure. Thanks for listening to another episode of On the Brink with Castle Island. To find out
more about Castle Island, visit castleisland.vc. To listen to all of our podcast episodes,
please go to onthebrink-podcast.com, or just click on the tab on our website. Thanks for listening.